[{"id": "601b4afd49076251badbeabf", "question": "What was the first food to be intentionally microwaved?", "answer": "Popcorn", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133995c", "question": "Who were the two villains in the movie \"Batman Returns\"?", "answer": "The Penguin and Catwoman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c730", "question": "What vitamin group, important for vision and bone growth, includes retinol?", "answer": "Vitamin A", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5feccf49ec223966ae8f88b4", "question": "How does Jill Masterson die in \"Goldfinger\"?", "answer": "Her skin is painted gold", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9c2", "question": "What is Albumen the correct term for?", "answer": "Egg White", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be4c", "question": "The Arabic word for \"season\" gave us what name for South Asia's rainy season?", "answer": "Monsoon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ef", "question": "In the book \"Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows\" what does the acronym RAB stand for?", "answer": "Regulus A. Black", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59067a4dff9c0647b50a8057", "question": "What country hosted the 2016 Summer Olympics?", "answer": "Brazil", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9bd", "question": "The Mario villain \"Wario\", made his first appearance in which Nintendo game?", "answer": "Super Mario Land 2", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac15", "question": "The Union of the Comoros is located on the northern end of which water channel?", "answer": "Mozambique Channel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b360", "question": "What were the wicks in the Vestal Virgins lamps allegedly made from?", "answer": "Asbestos", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5a4a974661d1b4d384d5d682", "question": "What nationality is designer Karl Lagerfield?", "answer": "German", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5904980dcf93664eb1048685", "question": "What is activated for freckles to appear?", "answer": "Melanocytes", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6008df6cf4f3bc4a292f862a", "question": "What did Zacchaeus do in order to catch a glimpse at Jesus Christ?", "answer": "Zacchaeus climbed a tree so he could have clear view of the Messiah on his way to Jericho.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396a5", "question": "The 1962 movie \"Lawrence of Arabia\" was based on the real-life exploits of whom?", "answer": "T.E. Lawrence", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133944d", "question": "Who narrates the movie \"Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels\"?", "answer": "Alan Ford", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4b38f06d333868d34d6d9", "question": "Which song produced a Christmas truce during World War I?", "answer": "\"Silent Night\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59ca3c2944f0f6af5b06662d", "question": "How does Wonder Woman control her invisible airplane?", "answer": "Mental powers", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a10", "question": "What does the sailor hold in his right hand on Margaret Thatcher's coat of arms?", "answer": "Binoculars", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7c5c2877e98cb977789b3", "question": "The \"Khyber Pass\" connects what two countries?", "answer": "Afghanistan and Pakistan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015fc8efe83fe1f2a824c42", "question": "What religious season do some churches observe for a few before and in relation to Christmas?", "answer": "Advent is held for a few weeks before Christmas.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2d2ba2596a59cbdfbd392", "question": "What is Virginia's state motto?", "answer": "Sic Semper Tyrannis", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "597742ce284458f1d7854422", "question": "What two Coaches on \"The Voice\" US have been on from season 1 through season 14?", "answer": "Blake Shelton and Adam Levine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b7ab8e46490a8cc1a6e528e", "question": "In \"The Adventures of Pinocchio\", who did Pinocchio accidentally kill?", "answer": "The Talking Cricket", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdc0f6b469bb8041d07a067", "question": "What is the term for cooking meats like pork or duck in order to melt some of the fat out of them?", "answer": "Rendering", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338919", "question": "Who runs the orphanage in the musical \"Annie\"?", "answer": "Miss Hannigan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fffa92473838c5c8a417f41", "question": "What material is the most expensive substance on earth?", "answer": "Antimatter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adee", "question": "What year did the English Civil War end?", "answer": "1651", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388f0", "question": "In the book \"Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince\", who does Harry catch tentacula leaves?", "answer": "Professor Horace Slughorn", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133991f", "question": "What was the name of the first spin-off from the TV show \"Law & Order\"?", "answer": "Law & Order: SVU", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aee8", "question": "Which battle saw the final defeat of the Jacobites in 1746?", "answer": "Battle of Culloden", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b556", "question": "What is Hershey's most popular product?", "answer": "Reeses Peanut Butter Cup", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ab977986faa38a764be529", "question": "On what vehicle was the Mutt Cutts Van based on in the 1994 film \"Dumb and Dumber\"?", "answer": "1984 Ford Econoline", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ad7", "question": "What novel begins with the words \"Marley was dead...\"?", "answer": "A Christmas Carol", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cae", "question": "Who wrote \"Tarzan of the Apes\" in 1912?", "answer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe768c8eec85e375820b2a7", "question": "The Ghirardelli Chocolate Company was founded in which city?", "answer": "San Francisco, California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff2148831a458464a93c458", "question": "A sentence, verse, etc., that includes all the letters of the alphabet is called what?", "answer": "Pangram", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd66c41a5bfecdd737e0891", "question": "What country is said to be the world\u2019s leading manufacturer of false teeth?", "answer": "Liechtenstein", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c57", "question": "What is the name of Sergeant Snorkle\u2019s dog in \u201cBeetle Bailey\u201d?", "answer": "Otto", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febb0b67e83c707845b2107", "question": "What was used to fill thermometers before mercury?", "answer": "Brandy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1b7", "question": "When did boxer John L. Sullivan die?", "answer": "1918", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aaf", "question": "Who wrote, Once Upon a Christmas in 1972?", "answer": "Pearl S. Buck", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe65551ae7e414034b5aeaf", "question": "Greek Mythology, who was responsible for the abduction of Persephone which led to the four seasons of the Earth?", "answer": "Hades", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60078a770eee65b76b9f2660", "question": "In the Zimmermann Telegram, Germany proposed an alliance to which nation?", "answer": "Mexico (In 1917, Germany proposed that Mexico could reconquer Texas, Arizona and New Mexico from America during World War.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe9f4f7ff048f679a45aace", "question": "Microphobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Small things", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b873", "question": "What company did Craig Newmark found?", "answer": "Craigslist", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcab", "question": "What four-letter clarified butter is commonly used in Indian cuisine?", "answer": "Ghee", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a702", "question": "What is the official state animal of Kansas?", "answer": "The bison", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a415", "question": "What US city is home to the annual \"All-American Soap Box Derby\"?", "answer": "Akron, Ohio", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abc1", "question": "Tirana is the capital of which Eastern European country?", "answer": "Albania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339902", "question": "What was the first Top 40 hit for Tom Petty & The Heartbreakers?", "answer": "Breakdown", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b008", "question": "What city in Idaho was the first in the world to use electricity generated by nuclear power?", "answer": "Arco", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5af98717aeb0982ee4559551", "question": "What is the famous forced march of the Cherokee from Georgia to Indian Country called?", "answer": "The Trail of Tears", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2eb", "question": "What US state has been led by Hannibal Hamlin and Edmund Muskie?", "answer": "Maine", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff145edb0ee8c595b6d39bd", "question": "What is Dr. Frankenstein's first name?", "answer": "Victor", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6000ed819a72b906b34e3ced", "question": "Who discovered the mathematical system of logarithms?", "answer": "John Napier", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fec866aec223966ae8f8810", "question": "What did writer Stephen King do with his royalty check he received for the film \"The Shawshank Redemption?", "answer": "King had the uncashed check framed and mailed it to the film's director, Frank Darabont.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c85f", "question": "What word did Alexander Graham Bell suggest for answering the phone?", "answer": "Ahoy", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af7b", "question": "The USS Arizona Memorial commemorates the victims of what event?", "answer": "Japanese bombing of Pearl Harbor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4db", "question": "In what country would you look for the Loch Ness Monster?", "answer": "Scotland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391b1", "question": "Who played the female lead role in the 2007 movie \"Stardust\"?", "answer": "Claire Danes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59e6bd51fb6c85e9e634ff66", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Antimony?", "answer": "Sb", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a3c83c4039f3d7859290ffb", "question": "In the TV Show \"Gunsmoke\", who portrayed deputy Chester Goode?", "answer": "Dennis Weaver", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1ca", "question": "For what crime was Bruno Hauptmann executed in 1936?", "answer": "Kidnapping the Lindbergh baby", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a622", "question": "What larger park is found in Manhattan?", "answer": "Central Park", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339986", "question": "What singer played the role of Uncle Jesse in the 2005 movie \"The Dukes of Hazzard\"?", "answer": "Willie Nelson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8ca", "question": "What San Francisco hill is home to a famous colony of wild parrots?", "answer": "Telegraph Hill", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a168", "question": "What is Tina Turner's real name?", "answer": "Anne Mae Bullock", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ef3", "question": "Which literary work's title character is named Henry Higgins?", "answer": "Pygmalion", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ad7eaebb24f84e0b9f9ffd9", "question": "What was Richard Wagner's second Opera that was inspired by a trip on the sea?", "answer": "The Flying Dutchman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fffa61c73838c5c8a417f2d", "question": "What is the process by which a Komodo Dragon can reproduce asexually?", "answer": "Parthenogenesis", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6a9e020565ad31a57c80c", "question": "Whose image is on the U.S. half-dollar from 1916 to 1947?", "answer": "Lady Liberty", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b57183c67df192a942e335c", "question": "Which stretch of water seperates Tierra del Fuego from the rest of South America?", "answer": "Strait of Magellan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b3589e25db0d66a186cb54f", "question": "French fries are claimed to have originated in which country?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5cefc09b948005ec986edcdd", "question": "Who is the fourth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Yeojin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60062a36c9d816e292245c15", "question": "What artist created a stained glass window for the United Nations?", "answer": "In 1964, a 15 by 12 foot stained glass window by\u00a0Marc Chagall\u00a0was donated to the United Nations to commemorate Dag Hammarskj\u00f6ld.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f3e", "question": "According to legend, who cut the tree-bark rope tied into a \"Gordian knot\"?", "answer": "Alexander the Great", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdff5bc1cf6db9ac4808ced", "question": "What city is home to the Spanish Steps?", "answer": "Rome, Italy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b246", "question": "The US's first law school for women was named for what cross-dressing Shakespearean character?", "answer": "Portia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0a2", "question": "In what decade was Prince Charles born?", "answer": "1940s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca9d", "question": "Na is the chemical symbol for which element?", "answer": "Sodium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b073", "question": "Who was the first Secretary of the Treasury of the United States?", "answer": "Alexander Hamilton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395f1", "question": "In The Simpsons, who developed a serious slot-machine gambling problem?", "answer": "Marge", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa77", "question": "What is the capital of Malawi?", "answer": "Lilongwe", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d28", "question": "What children's books character is friends with Christopher Robin?", "answer": "Winnie the Pooh", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c13b", "question": "Who said \"You'd be surprised how much it costs to look this cheap\"?", "answer": "Dolly Parton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c7a", "question": "What war is the setting for the novel \"All Quiet on the Western Front\"?", "answer": "World War I", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a289", "question": "The Heavy Young Heathens cover \"The House of the Rising Sun\" on the soundtrack of which 2016 remake?", "answer": "The Magnificent Seven", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ee0", "question": "What literary villain died during a struggle at Reichenbach Falls?", "answer": "Professor Moriarty", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fefa5e36ce05a3942286ec5", "question": "What real American Revolution battle served as inspiration for the film \"The Patriot?\"", "answer": "The Battle of Cowpens", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe93d046bd93ce3a4e5f6ae", "question": "Who invented the telescope?", "answer": "Hans Lipperhey (or Lippershey)", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2ee", "question": "What US state has been led by William McKinley and Salmon P. Chase?", "answer": "Ohio", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6bd", "question": "On a standard color wheel, what color is opposite blue?", "answer": "Orange", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f47", "question": "What is the real first name of Tyler Perry's famous character, Madea?", "answer": "Mabe", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f16a05f7c52aae91cc07d7", "question": "What state is the oldest US commercial pretzel bakery located in?", "answer": "Pennsylvania", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff258e431a458464a93c468", "question": "What was the purpose of the \"Moustache Guard\"?", "answer": "To protect the mustache while eating", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c209", "question": "Which country were the 1912 Summer Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba38", "question": "What nickname was given to the Indianapolis Motor Speedway in 1909?", "answer": "Brickyard", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a30a", "question": "What character did Natascha McElhone play on the TV show \"Californication\"?", "answer": "Karen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59049e53cf93664eb10486b3", "question": "The Koson District is a district in the Qashqadaryo Region of which country?", "answer": "Uzbekistan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59c1ceb47bd84c0ea43ad43a", "question": "Who is Thomas John Woodward better known as?", "answer": "Tom Jones", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59e6b752fb6c85e9e634ff4b", "question": "What does \"Rx\" mean to a pharmacist?", "answer": "A medical prescription", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff3c2194f032c0db195b47e", "question": "Where did the Battle of Bunker Hill take place?", "answer": "Although Bunker Hill was the main objective of the colonists and British military, most of the fighting occurred on Breed's Hill.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab3e", "question": "Juba is the capital of which country?", "answer": "South Sudan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe65644ae7e414034b5aec5", "question": "Which philosophical movement defined the Renaissance?", "answer": "Humanism", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fec8b8bec223966ae8f883f", "question": "Who does the voice over for Dory from \"Finding Nemo\" and \"Finding Dory\"?", "answer": "Ellen DeGeneres", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "597cd6dbe347d002c297e4bd", "question": "\"Diamants sur canap\u00e9\" is the French translation of what American film?", "answer": "Breakfast at Tiffany's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbd2", "question": "How many \"herbs and spices\" does KFC claim to have in their \"secret recipe\"?", "answer": "11", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa54bdc73aa70ea0b70b1e", "question": "Which country (and it's territories) cover the most time zones?", "answer": "France and its eight territories cover 12 time zones.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a862", "question": "The popular tourist destination, Amalfi, is located in which Italian region?", "answer": "Campania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6017373744491cbd7c5a1786", "question": "What is the name of the iron-clad ship that engaged the CSS Virginia during the American Civil War?", "answer": "On March 9, 1862, the CSS Virginia engaged the USS Monitor off Hampton Roads, Virginia in a naval battle that resulted in a draw.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339133", "question": "\"The Faerie Queene\" is an incomplete epic poem by which English poet?", "answer": "Edmund Spenser", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe1efcf145fb2946670738e", "question": "What is the Japanese art of flower arrangement called?", "answer": "Ikebana", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339210", "question": "Who played the role of the Joker in the 1989 \"Batman\" movie?", "answer": "Jack Nicholson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b323700bf195a31e15d73c1", "question": "Which supermodel is nicknamed \"The Body\"?", "answer": "Elle Macpherson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b376", "question": "Who was the last woman to be hanged in Britain in the 1950's?", "answer": "Ruth Ellis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c06", "question": "What year was Marvin Gaye shot and killed by his father?", "answer": "1984", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c544", "question": "What beam derives its name from \"light amplification by stimulated emission of radiation\"?", "answer": "Laser beam", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe655e3ae7e414034b5aebd", "question": "What Greek figure was famously forced to complete 12 Labors?", "answer": "Hercules", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339480", "question": "What is the name of Goldie Hawn's daughter who starred in the 2000 movie \"Almost Famous\"?", "answer": "Kate Hudson", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fa4", "question": "Poseidon was the Greek god of what?", "answer": "Sea", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe69b9820565ad31a57c761", "question": "Jimmy Carter served in which military branch?", "answer": "U.S. Navy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bc6", "question": "What was the name of the ship that Jason & his Argonauts sail in?", "answer": "Argo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397ce", "question": "What TV show began with the words \"Space, the final frontier\"?", "answer": "Star Trek", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5af255deb63e5727cf5a483b", "question": "Which of Antigua and Barbuda\u2019s islands is the largest by land area?", "answer": "Antigua", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58f5661133a95c66dc4fe75e", "question": "Which British opera festival was started in 1934?", "answer": "Glyndebourne", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5f164acef9b80650dbe7f92c", "question": "How many British Admiral-class battlecruisers were cancelled in 1919?", "answer": "Three", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339878", "question": "In Star Trek, what planet is Spock from?", "answer": "Vulcan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4d1", "question": "Which two numbers are used in the binary system?", "answer": "Zero and one", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133986a", "question": "In Disney's \"Cinderella\", what is the cats name?", "answer": "Lucifer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a9", "question": "Who voices the character of scientist and inventor Professor John I.Q. Nerdelbaum Frink Jr. on \"The Simpsons\"?", "answer": "Hank Azaria", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab57", "question": "Which former Soviet Republic in Central Asia has Tashkent as its capital?", "answer": "Uzbekistan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8d2", "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Colorado river?", "answer": "Mexico", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af82", "question": "Who died three months into his 4th term as president?", "answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597cd505e347d002c297e4b3", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"The Last of the Mohicans\", first published in 1826?", "answer": "James Fenimore Cooper", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba00", "question": "What sport did hall-of-famer Honus Wagner play?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b7ffb533a3a814d89068c64", "question": "Whose autobiography is titled \"Long Walk to Freedom\"?", "answer": "Nelson Mandela's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339be3", "question": "In what year was actor Johnny Depp born?", "answer": "1963", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338eac", "question": "What short story begins \"$1.87. That was all. And sixty cents of it was in pennies\"?", "answer": "The Gift of the Magi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b193", "question": "What year did Napoleon become the Emperor of the French?", "answer": "1804", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b468", "question": "What year did Ferdinand Porsche and his team started to design the VW Beetle?", "answer": "1934", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c24f", "question": "What do you call the feeling of having experienced something before?", "answer": "Deja vu", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae64", "question": "On July 4, 1776, how many English colonies proclaimed a Declaration of Independence?", "answer": "13", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea49f5ff048f679a45abbe", "question": "A buck, or male deer, is also called a what?", "answer": "Stag", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fc5", "question": "What famous murders inspired Alfred Hitchcock's film \"Rope\"?", "answer": "The Leopold and Loeb killings", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ec22b48dc25ca9e12ef62a", "question": "Which French singer and actor sings the theme song to Disney's film \"The Aristocats\"?", "answer": "Maurice Chevalier", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d52", "question": "What Herman Melville character always answers \"I would prefer not to\" whenever his boss asks him to work?", "answer": "Bartleby the Scrivener", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cc3", "question": "What was the one-syllable catchphrase of Little Orphan Annie's dog, Sandy?", "answer": "Arf", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bab9", "question": "Sauerbraten is a specialty beef dish that originated in what country?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fede62a6ce05a3942286df7", "question": "How many times do you actually see the knife stabbing Marion in the shower scene of \"Psycho\"?", "answer": "None", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339563", "question": "Bill Melendez directed which Christmas TV special?", "answer": "A Charlie Brown Christmas", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339df5", "question": "What red wine does Paul Giamatti refuse to drink in the movie \"Sideways\"?", "answer": "Merlot", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59f9bb7d364247bf200fb8a4", "question": "Which UK group won the 1981 Eurovision Song Contest?", "answer": "Bucks Fizz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c752", "question": "Who invented the equals symbol?", "answer": "Robert Recorde", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a073", "question": "In the film \"Saving Private Ryan\" what was Private Ryan's first name?", "answer": "James", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5eb", "question": "What type of garment are \"Elephant bells\"?", "answer": "Pants", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba2c", "question": "Which US state's official flower is the Saguato Cactus?", "answer": "Arizona", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c35a", "question": "What is the most obvious physical difference between snails and slugs?", "answer": "The shell", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8b53101dd7bf43be5e7cc", "question": "What is the name for the process of electing a Pope?", "answer": "Conclave", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afe5", "question": "Who did George Bush Sr. defeat in the election in 1988?", "answer": "Michael Dukakis", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f89", "question": "Who is the author of the book \"The Life-changing Magic of Tidying Up\"?", "answer": "Marie Kondo", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5c4", "question": "Sleeping Bear Dunes National Park is located along the shores of what lake?", "answer": "Lake Michigan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdc9", "question": "Is it true that the Special Sauce on a Big Mac is Thousand Island Dressing?", "answer": "No, it has more ingredients", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff670f552a821ff76ae8b23", "question": "Who invented \"Jell-O\"?", "answer": "Pearle Wait", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c072", "question": "What is the Shaddock a variety of?\u00a0", "answer": "Citrus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b26f", "question": "In 1991, who erected three thousand blue and yellow umbrellas on the coasts of California and Japan?", "answer": "Christo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a74a", "question": "What US city is serviced by Dulles International Airport?", "answer": "Washington D.C.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae69", "question": "What did Ronald Reagan disclose he was suffering from in 1994?", "answer": "Alzheimer's Disease", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339216", "question": "What fictional Kansas town is the earthly home of the young Superman?", "answer": "Smallville", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5921fbfea4edfd43a087adbe", "question": "What is the symbol of the Zodiac sign Leo?", "answer": "The Lion", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea48b7ff048f679a45abb2", "question": "What natural biological defense system protects the body from disease and fights off germs?", "answer": "Immunity", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5bbc92f460f0007efaba0e59", "question": "What is the name of Roy Rogers' horse?", "answer": "Trigger", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bcb", "question": "In what English city was Boy George born?", "answer": "London", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015f82dfe83fe1f2a824c29", "question": "When was Queen Elizabeth II born?", "answer": "She was born on April 21, 1926 at 2:40 A.M.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf4e", "question": "Angelo Sicilano better know as who?", "answer": "Charles Atlas", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5937eaaf08d98002fdd633a6", "question": "Easter Island is part of which country?", "answer": "Chile", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b32316fbf195a31e15d7384", "question": "Who wrote the opera \"Madama Butterfly\"?", "answer": "Giacomo Puccini", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7ef", "question": "What landmark is 250 feet long, 66 feet tall, and has a face modeled after the Pharaoh Khafre?", "answer": "The Sphinx", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff20ec831a458464a93c429", "question": "A person who writes the text of an opera, or other long vocal work, is called what?", "answer": "Librettist", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a570", "question": "What US city is famous for its French Quarter?", "answer": "New Orleans", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b699098e762b54eb9be9412", "question": "How is the number 20 written with Roman numerals?", "answer": "XX", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58c8a51a90aac110e4167071", "question": "What is Homer Simpson\u2019s beer of choice?", "answer": "Duff", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c064", "question": "In the video game \"God of War\", which mythological character must Kratos defeat at the end to finish the game?", "answer": "Ares (the God of War)", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef64f86ce05a3942286e68", "question": "What breed of dog portrayed Toto in 1939's \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "Cairn terrier", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bca6", "question": "Who is pictures on the US Purple Heart medal?", "answer": "George Washington", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c15", "question": "According to Exodus, what is the fifth plague of Egypt?", "answer": "Diseased livestock", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339758", "question": "How many kids does Uncle Buck take care of in the movie of the same name?", "answer": "Three", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133923c", "question": "What street do the women of \"Desperate Housewives\" live on?", "answer": "Wisteria Lane", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339051", "question": "The tune \"Rhapsody in Blue\" was first performed in which year?", "answer": "1924", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fecc32dec223966ae8f887b", "question": "What singer staged a comeback with \"The Emancipation of Mimi,\" the second-best-selling album worldwide in 2005?", "answer": "Mariah Carey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca07", "question": "The first integral of acceleration gives us what?", "answer": "Velocity", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ffa3acfc73aa70ea0b70ae1", "question": "What is the highest waterfall in Europe?", "answer": "The\u00a0Krimml Waterfalls", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fef631a6ce05a3942286e62", "question": "Who was the first guest on \"Late Night with David Letterman\"?", "answer": "Bill Murray", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcd5", "question": "In England, what is governed by the FA?", "answer": "Soccer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c105", "question": "What is the meaning of the Latin phrase \"cum grano salis\"?", "answer": "With a grain of salt", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d58", "question": "Who created the comic book character Wonder Woman?", "answer": "William Moulton Marston", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b290", "question": "Who was the first US president to die in office?", "answer": "William Harrison", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6f2", "question": "What device was Alexander Graham Bell working, which led him to the invention of the telephone?", "answer": "Hearing aid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b004", "question": "What city hosted the 1984 Summer Olympics?", "answer": "Los Angeles", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfa1", "question": "A \"pigskin\" is another name for what?", "answer": "A Football", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d5e", "question": "What are the names of the main characters of the \"Twilight\" book series?", "answer": "Bella and Edward", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adbf", "question": "Which two public figures were assassinated in the United States in 1968?", "answer": "Martin Luther King Jr. and Robert Kennedy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5c88e6db22f44c2d77a29c43", "question": "Qeru Chay is a village in which country?", "answer": "Iran", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be80", "question": "What's the only Grand Slam tennis event still played on grass?", "answer": "Wimbledon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cb9", "question": "What TV show featured the fictional \"The Kings of Queens\" fraternity?", "answer": "All in the Family", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd66a28a5bfecdd737e0880", "question": "Where is the last remaining Blockbuster store?", "answer": "Bend, Oregon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff3c2c54f032c0db195b485", "question": "In 1912, what did a Paris orphanage give away as prizes when it held a raffle to raise money?", "answer": "Live babies", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d0c", "question": "What historical event provides the backdrop for the 1905 novel \"The Scarlet Pimpernel\"?", "answer": "The French Revolution", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7349eeec85e375820b239", "question": "The Colossus of Rhodes was dedicated to which god?", "answer": "Helios", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff0b559e662d71a53650ff8", "question": "In Jane Austen's \"Pride and Prejudice,\" what is Mr. Darcy's first name?", "answer": "Fitzwilliam", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea7815ff048f679a45abd3", "question": "What is the tallest type of horse?", "answer": "Shire", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c72a", "question": "What constellation's Latin name translates as \"Smaller Bear\" or \"Little Bear\"?", "answer": "Ursa Minor", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338efc", "question": "Which literary work's title character is named Frankie Addams?", "answer": "The Member of the Wedding", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aae8", "question": "Ghana is located along which gulf?", "answer": "Gulf of Guinea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391da", "question": "Who voiced the character Gru from the animated movie \"Despicable Me\"?", "answer": "Steve Carell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febd4ca7e83c707845b2160", "question": "In the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\", which character had his hands replaced by the director, Frank Darabont, as insert shot?", "answer": "Andy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339562", "question": "In the movie It's a Wonderful Life, what did George dream of becoming?", "answer": "An architect", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4a990761d1b4d384d5d695", "question": "What year was the radio show \"Gunsmoke\" adapted for TV?", "answer": "1955", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff7bf6e2b316f4693fb6793", "question": "Who wrote, sang, and played the instruments for \"Wonderful Christmastime\"?", "answer": "Paul McCartney", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff14051b0ee8c595b6d399a", "question": "Who was the first African-American Pulitzer Prize winner?", "answer": "Gwendolyn Brooks", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febd3eb7e83c707845b2157", "question": "Red had how many parole hearings through out the course of the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "Three", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ff0", "question": "What film coined the term \"cameo appearance\" for a brief star turn in a movie?", "answer": "Around the World in Eighty Days", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdd5f8a0499cffc60b84236", "question": "Who was the founder of the Mongol Empire?", "answer": "Genghis Khan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac9b", "question": "Who was prime minister of the United Kingdom from 1997 to 2007?", "answer": "Tony Blair", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c4d8", "question": "What fruit comes in Bartlett and Bosc variety?", "answer": "Pears", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbe2", "question": "What petroleum company merged with Exxon in 1999?", "answer": "Mobil Corporation, formally known as Standard Oil of New York or Socony, merged with Exxon, which resulted in a new company called ExxonMobil.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caa2", "question": "With what is sulfur and saltpeter mixed to make gunpowder?", "answer": "Charcoal", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c82", "question": "Who wrote \"The Legend of Sleepy Hollow\"?", "answer": "Washington Irving", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015f975fe83fe1f2a824c33", "question": "What does the final day of Passover celebrate?", "answer": "The arrival of the Israelites to the Red Sea", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe528ec1bf59ab7d2e380ff", "question": "What classic school pet is considered a delicacy in Peru?", "answer": "Guinea pig", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe4ec1406d333868d34d760", "question": "The name \"Australia\" was formally adopted in which year?", "answer": "1824", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bec", "question": "What musical featured \"I Could Have Danced All Night\"?", "answer": "My Fair Lady", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fd0", "question": "What TV show did \"Fraiser\" spin off from?", "answer": "Cheers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d15", "question": "What comic strip features a family dog named Barfy?", "answer": "The Family Circus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe6a6f720565ad31a57c7e3", "question": "What is considered the turning point of World War II in Europe?", "answer": "Battle of Stalingrad", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1e4", "question": "Which US president lived in Springwood?", "answer": "Franklin Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff145dbb0ee8c595b6d39bc", "question": "The pen name of which American writer means \"two fathoms deep\"?", "answer": "Mark Twain", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5f164eaaf9b80650dbe7f936", "question": "What color is the \"Mind stone\" in the 2017 Marvel Legacy relaunch?", "answer": "Yellow", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7a1", "question": "What year was inventor Alexander Graham Bell born in?", "answer": "1847", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397d3", "question": "What country singer released the album \"Pieces of the Sky\"?", "answer": "Emmylou Harris", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c54d", "question": "Kimberlite contains what precious stone?", "answer": "Diamond", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0ce", "question": "What sport is the Heisman Trophy awarded in?", "answer": "American college football", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdc1522469bb8041d07a089", "question": "Where is the famous haunted house located that was the subject of books and films following the murder of the DeFeo family?", "answer": "Amityville, Long Island, New York", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f17804eb8195c09b948d5c0", "question": "What are the suction-like cups on a gecko's toes that allows it to attach itself to any surface called?", "answer": "Setae", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ebc", "question": "What Broadway musical featured the song \"Solla Sollew\"?", "answer": "Seussical", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a737", "question": "Which US state is home to Craters of the Moon National Monument?", "answer": "Idaho", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe7c642877e98cb977789b5", "question": "Bibimbap is a traditional rice dish from which region?", "answer": "Korea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac91", "question": "Which Egyptian queen is said to have died following a bite from an asp?", "answer": "Cleopatra", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe9f6b4ff048f679a45aadd", "question": "What did Albert Einstein win the Nobel Prize for in 1921?", "answer": "For his discovery of the law of the photoelectric effect", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339320", "question": "What was the name of Bill and Ted's rock band in the movie \"Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure\"?", "answer": "Wild Stallions", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecc8ceec223966ae8f8893", "question": "What term is used in describing a situation where a golfer scores 8 on a hole?", "answer": "\"Snowman\"", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b57d", "question": "What ingredient does the word \"sushi\" refer to?", "answer": "Rice", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c97", "question": "What TV show takes place in the fictional city of Mockingbird Heights?", "answer": "The Munsters", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcc9", "question": "Who was sent to the electric chair on the testimony of her brother David Greenglass?", "answer": "Ethel Rosenberg", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a71e", "question": "What southern city is located on the shores of Lake Pontchartrain?", "answer": "New Orleans", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea46ffff048f679a45aba7", "question": "What does \"PO\" stand for on a prescription?", "answer": "By mouth", "category": "science"}]